filmsforaction.org 2018-12-26

# About Films For Action - Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, make a donation, add comments on site content, or edit your profile information. 

When registering on our site, you will be asked to enter your first and last name and your e-mail address. We strongly encourage our site members to use their real name, so that your friends can find you on the site and to help cut down on many of the problems associated with anonymity on the web. We understand in some cases the necessity of maintaining anonymity (such as if the user writes articles on controvertial topics that might jepordize their job or real-word reputation). In these situations and at your discretion, you may visit our site anonymously. However, if it appears someone is abusing this privelege simply to be a jerk or to be disruptive, we won't be as sympathetic to these problems than if you used your real name.

After registering, you may add further details to your profile including your birthday, location, political views, website, about me description, profile picture, and other information tailored to help foster real-word connections with others of like interest. **

What information do we collect when I create an account using Facebook Connect?

**

When creating an account with Facebook Connect, we will pull data from your Facebook account to help create your Films For Action account. This includes your name, birthday, location, political views, website, about me description, and profile picture. We do not ask for your email address, but you can add this by going to your profile's account page (click "Settings" >> Account). After registering, you will be able to edit your profile as you wish, removing or adding anything as preferred. We will also look for any friends you have on Facebook that are members of Films For Action and add them to the people you are "following."

**What privacy settings do I have for my profile?**

By default, a users profile is public and can be viewed by non-registered users of the site. If you would like to include more private information on your profile we offer users three privacy settings. This gives you the option to only display your profile details to 1) everyone, 2) only other registered members on the site, or 3) only people you "follow." Your name, profile picture, comments, and the content you've added will always remain public.

**What about the ads?**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/privacy/faq.html) enables it to serve ads based on visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us and other members to understand where you are coming from and to help you connect with others on the site who have similar interests.

• To improve our website

   We continually strive to improve our website's features based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

• To process donations

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of processing your donation.  
> 

• To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for registering or suscribing to our newsletter will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to Films For Action, website changes or additions, and strategic campaign updates. We will only email you when we think it's important.  
> 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you make a donation or enter, submit, or access your personal profile information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards and billing address information) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us keep track of whether you are logged in or not, and to save your preferences for future visits.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'Settings' page located at the top-right of the site when you are logged in.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website and the information contained on it is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://www.filmsforaction.org/About/SiteTerms/>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions, comments or concerns regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. We have a great respect for our members privacy and have taken care to ensure our members privacy is protected. We welcome any suggestions to further improve the privacy options for members of the site.

https://www.filmsforaction.org/Contact
